收音机∶现在是凌晨2点25分,这首歌送给那些仍然在等待情人的人,
Radio: It's two twenty five am and this is for all you lovers who still
仍然相信她这么晚还没回来是因为堵车的缘故.
believe she's stuck in traffic.
迈克∶对,很可能是堵车,凯特很有可能是被堵在路上了,但是剧院周围的路都可以通往校园.
Mike: Yeah, that's probably it, Kate's probably just stuck in traffic,
好了,我就再多给她5分钟,如果她2点半还不回来的话,那我就回家了.
I mean, the theatre
is all the way across campus.OK, I'll give her five more minutes, if she's
not here by two thirty, I'm going home
(迈克开始回忆戏剧表演中的最后的一段情节)
(In Mike's head from the play in the last episode)
凯特∶我不能马上就决定我的一生.
Kate: I can't decide my whole life in a moment.
迈克∶我们只有一会的时间了.
Mike: Well a moment's all we got.
凯特∶哦!迈克!
Kate: Oh, Oh Mike!
迈克∶哦!凯特,我再也不能隐藏我从你的感情了!我希望我可以,但是,我真的不行!也许这样做是错的!
Mike: Oh Kate, I can't hide my feelings from you any more; I wish I could but I can't.Maybe this is wrong!
凯特∶不,不,没有错.
Kate: No, no, it's not wrong.
迈克∶我们向戴维去解释.
Mike: Look, we'll explain to David.
凯特∶是的,我们要告诉他,我们并不是有意要让它发生的.
Kate: Yeah, yeah, we'll just tell him that we didn't plan for it to happen.
迈克∶对,我们甚至都不希望它发生.
Mike: And...and that we didn't even want it to happen.
凯特∶他会明白的.
Kate: Yeah, he'll understand.
迈克∶恩,是的,他是一个不错的家伙.
Mike: Oh, yeah, he's a great guy.
凯特∶恩,啊,他是一个不错的家伙.
Kate: Ah, he's a great great guy!
迈克∶不错的家伙.
Mike: A great guy.
戴维∶好你们2个!你们演的太好了!宝贝,
David:You Guys, you guys were great!
我知道最近几个礼拜我的表现差到了极点,但是,
Oh look, honey, I know I've been a total jerk for the last few weeks,
我知道我们可以重新来过,凯蒂,我爱你.
but I know we can get things back the way they were, Katie.I love you.
索恩教授∶好了,到谢幕的时间了.
Professor Thorn: Alright people, it's time for the bows.
戴维∶我们走!
David: Let's go!
迈克∶哦天啦,她可能去哪里了呢?表演都已经结束了几个小时了.
Mike: Oh man, where could she be?The play's been over for hours.
收音机∶现在是凌晨2点半,路上没有任何的交通堵塞!
Radio: Two thirty in the morning and by the way, there's no traffic...
她不会来了.
anywhere!She's not coming.
迈克∶好吧,好吧,我再多给她5分钟,要是还不回来的话,
Mike: Alright, alright, I'll give her five minutes and then I'm out of here.
我就走.好,好,最后一分钟,我不等了.
Alright, alright, one more minute and I'm calling it a night.
杰森∶我知道你的感觉.
Jason: I know how you feel.
迈克∶爸爸,这么晚你怎么还没睡?
Mike: Hi Dad, err...what are you doing still up?
杰森∶拿晨报.
Jason: Getting the morning paper.
迈克∶哦!
Mike: Oh.
杰森∶你刚进门?
Jason: You just getting in?
迈克∶呃..
Mike: Err...
杰森∶你在凯特的房间里过夜,对吗?
Jason: You spent the night at Kate's, didn't you?
迈克∶呃..
Mike: Err...
杰森∶别否认迈克,我看到过你吻她的样子了!
Jason: Don't deny it Mike, I saw the way you kissed her!
迈克∶呃..
Mike: Err...
杰森∶这就是你的表现,不是吗?
Jason: That's where you were, wasn't it?
杰森∶呃...是.
Mike: Err...Yeah.
杰森∶啊,天啦.幸好你妈妈没有听到...
Jason: Ah, God, I'm glad your mother isn't alive to hear this.
迈克∶什么?
Mike: What?
杰森:对不起,这太早了,
Jason: I'm sorry, it's early, I'm a little groggy;
我还不能接受.
I had to come up with something.
迈克:爸爸,放松,
Mike: Well, relax Dad, I spent the whole night in my car...
我是一个人在车里过夜的,等着凯特.
alone, waiting for Kate.
杰森∶迈克,太凄惨了.
Jason: Oh, Mike, that's pathetic.
迈克∶谢谢你爸爸,谢谢你的可怜.
Mike: Thank you Dad, for that boost.
杰森∶对不起迈克,等我喝杯咖啡后,
Jason: Sorry Mike, I didn't think we'd hit on anything this important
我们再来谈谈这么重要的事情.你去哪里?
before my morning coffee.Where you going?
迈克∶回到我的房间,去洗个澡,
Mike: Up to my room so I can shower and get to school,
然后去学校,
find out where Kate's first class is,
找出凯特第一堂课的教室,
get there and ask her where she was last night.
去问问她昨天晚上去哪里了.你是不是觉得这样也很凄惨?
Or is that too pathetic for you?
杰森∶既然你自己提出来了,迈克!迈克,如果你说那个女孩很爱你,但是她却整个晚上都不回家,也许是你曲解了她对你的感觉.嘿,不要,不要再去找她谈了.
Jason: Well now that you bring it up, Mike, yeah!You know, Mike, if this girl that you say is so nuts about you isn't coming home all night, maybe you're misinterpreting her feelings for you.Hey, just...just don't go out of your way to talk to her.
迈克:不用爸爸,她是我戏剧班的同学.
Mike: I don't have to Dad, she's in my drama class!
杰森∶你没听出我的真正意思;我是说在她和她的男朋友没有完全分手前,你不能去追她.
Jason: You're missing the point; you can't go chasing this girl around;
你应该去换一个班,找别的女孩,
not until she's worked out whatever she has to work out with her boyfriend.
找2个,或3个!
You gotta find another class, find another girl, find two, find three!
迈克∶哦,
Mike: Oh, so just to be honourable,
为了能光明正大,
I'm supposed to switch to the seven am drama class,
我就得换上7点钟的戏剧课,然后把自己的注意力转移到一个接一个,
and I'm then supposed to distract myself with one beautiful girl after
一个接一个的漂亮女孩身上!
another, after another, after another!
杰森∶那你想听我说什么,迈克?你想我说,别管羞耻了?
Jason: Well, what do you want to hear from me, Mike?
别理会给戴维带来的伤害?嘿,快去努力争取?
You wanna hear, forget honour?Forget about hurting David?Hey, just go for it.
迈克∶听起来不错.
Mike: That would be good.
杰森∶那你就找错人了.
Jason: Well, you came to the wrong guy.
索恩教授∶好了,
Professor Thorn: Alright, present this to the registrar,
把这个给注册处就行了,明天早上7点整要见到你哦.
and I will see you tomorrow morning at seven a.m sharp.Mr.
西维尔先生,
Seaver, you're entitled to switch your classes around, of course,
当然你有权换班,但是在我看来,
but you don't strike me as the sort of student who would relish an early
你好像不是那种愿意每天早晨提前开始学习的学生.
morning commencement to his academic day.
杰森∶呃...请再说一次.
Mike: Err...pardon me.
索恩教授∶我从来没有觉得你是个早起的人..
Professor Thorn: I never pegged you for an early bird geek
迈克∶在我姐姐的影响下,我现在已经是一半的早起的人了.呃....请原谅.
Mike: Well, I'm half geek on my sister's side.Oh, err...pardon me.
辛蒂∶索恩教授,正如你说的,我每时每刻都很努力的学习,我认为我现在终于可以读莎士比亚了.
Cindy: Any time.Professor Thorn, I worked real hard, like you said,
S.H.A.K.... and I think I've finally got Shakespeare.S.H.A.K..
杰森∶(在迈克的脑海里)找另一个女孩.
Jason: (In Mike's head) Find another girl Mike.
辛蒂∶不,不,不,不要帮我!
Cindy: No, no, no, don't help me!
索恩教授∶我不会的,月亮女神.
Professor Thorn: Would that I could, Cynthia.
辛蒂∶该死的,总是记不住那些元音.
Cindy: Darn, it's always the vowels.
索恩教授∶对.
Professor Thorn: Yes.
迈克∶啊...好了.
Mike: Ah...no it's OK.
辛蒂∶不,我敢肯定这个单词中没有"o".
Cindy: No, I'm sure there's no O in either word.
迈克∶我....
Mike: See I...
辛蒂∶N! D! Y!我的名字!
Cindy: N!D!Y!That's my name!
迈克∶我觉得你很适合我.
Mike: You know, you know, you're perfect for me.
辛蒂∶迈克,
Cindy: Wait a second, Mike.
等等.我们在一个班上呆了一个学期,
We've been in this class together all semester and you've never given
你都没有约过我.
me the time of day.
迈克∶哦,可能是我现在觉得自己已经做好约你这样的女孩的准备了.
Mike: Well...well that's because I guess I've never been ready for a girl
嘿,今天晚上怎么样?
like you.You know, hey what about tonight?
可以去看个电影,吃个晚餐,
Maybe a movie, dinner, just a fun night with no spelling whatsoever.
只是过一个没有拼写的开心的晚上.你觉得怎么样?
What do you say?
辛蒂∶我说,Y.E.X.
Cindy: I say, Y.E.X.
迈克∶太好了,太好了.我要离开这里了.
Mike: Very, very good.Errm...listen, I gotta get out of here.
凯特∶迈克,教室在这边.
Kate: Mike, class is this way.
迈克∶哦!我已经更改了上课时间了.
Mike: Oh, I transferred out.
凯特∶迈克,等等.
Kate: Mike, hold on.
迈克∶凯特,听着,你的课马上就要开始了.
Mike: Listen Kate, your class is starting.
凯特∶我想和你谈谈.
Kate: Well, I'd like to talk about this.
迈克∶我知道, 但是你的课马上就要开始了.
Mike: I know, but your class is starting.
凯特∶我昨天晚上本来想打电话给你的,看看我要你...
Kate: Look, I wanted to call you last night, see what I want you...
辛蒂∶迈克,我忘了你说今天晚上几点钟来接我了.
Cindy: Mike, about tonight, I forgot what time you were picking me up.
迈克∶哦,我还没说呢.
Mike: Oh, err, well I didn't say.
辛蒂∶哦,那就好,这样我就不会觉得不好意思了.
Cindy: Oh, oh good, now I don't feel so bad.
迈克∶辛蒂,辛蒂,8点钟.
Mike: Cindy, Cindy, Eight o' clock.
辛蒂:好好,我这次记住了.
Cindy: Oh, oh, OK.I'll remember this time.
迈克∶恩,恩,你刚才说你本来想打电话给我的?
Mike: Ah, ah, so you were gonna say that you wanted to call me.
凯特∶我要上课了.
Kate: Class is starting.
杰森∶哦,戴维.
Mike: Ooh, David.
戴维∶嘿,迈克,
David: Hey, Mike, if we don't watch where we're going,
如果我们不当心我们前面的路,其中一个肯定是要受伤的.
one of us is gonna get hurt.
迈克∶说说看.
Mike: Tell me about it.
辛蒂∶我还是不明白.
Cindy: I'm still confused.
迈克∶恩,恩,你对电影还有什么没弄清楚的?
Mike: OK, OK, what exactly didn't you get about the movie?
辛蒂∶恩,为什么塞维·蔡斯每次度假都会发生不好的事情,
Cindy: Well, why does Chevy Chase keep going on vacation when only bad
但是他却还是要去呢?
things happen?
迈克∶因为...呃,我也不知道.
Mike: Well, because...err...Heck, I don't know.
辛蒂:好吧,难道他从来就没有意识到孩子的不同么?
Cindy: OK, OK, well then how come he never notices that he has different kids?
艾克∶辛蒂,我不知道你会不会,
Mike: Errm...look Cindy, I don't know about you,
但是呢,对我来说,有时想的太多就会头痛.
but sometimes thinking too much gives me a headache.
辛蒂∶迈克,你真聪明.
Cindy: You're so wise, Mike.
迈克∶辛蒂,我不能这样做.
Mike: Cindy, I can't do this.
辛蒂∶哦,好的,哦,好些了吗?
Cindy: Oh, right, oh...better?
迈克∶不,不,不,
Mike: No, no, no, Cindy, it has nothing to do with your breath,
辛蒂,和你的呼吸没关,
it's just that, when I asked you out I...
只是,当我约你出来的时候,并不是出于正常的理由.
I did it for not the normal reasons.
辛蒂∶迈克,你怎么了?
Cindy: What exactly are you into?
本∶迈克,妈妈要我告诉你...你好.
Ben: Mike, Mom says to tell you...Well hello.
辛蒂∶你好,我是辛蒂.
Cindy: Hi, I'm Cindy.
本∶事实上还没有我高.
Ben: And I'm actually taller than you are.
迈克∶呃,本,妈妈要你告诉我什么?
Mike: Err, Ben, Mom said to tell me what?
本∶要你和我分享,迈克,要你和我分享.
Ben: To share, Mike...to share.
迈克∶本,出去!出去!出去!
Mike: Ben, get out!Get out!Get out!
本∶哦,我打扰你们了?那我就不说了.
Ben: Oh, am I in the way here?Say no more.
迈克∶呃...本,我不是那个意思..
Mike: Oh...err...Ben, I didn't mean...
本∶我知道你就是这个意思.
Ben: I know what you mean.
辛蒂∶我们刚说到什么了?
Cindy: Now, where were we?
迈克∶辛蒂,
Mike: Look Cindy, I'm trying to explain to you;
我想跟你解释因为我请你出来只是为了转移注意力.
I only went out with you as a diversion.
我是说我约你出来就是为了得到你的身体.
I mean, I only wanted you for you body.
辛蒂∶巧极了!我要你也是为了我的身体!
Cindy: What a coincidence!I only want...I only wanted you for my body, too!
迈克∶辛蒂!
Mike: Cindy!
辛蒂∶迈克,难道我有什么不好吗?
Cindy: Mike, is there something wrong with me?
迈克∶那好吧,我不得不说出来了,
Mike: Alright!Alright, alright, I'll just come out with and say it;
是因为你的拼写.
it's your...your spelling.
戴维∶迈克,我不得不...哦,抱歉,我不是有意要打断你们.
David: Mike, I have to...Ooh, sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt anything here.
辛蒂∶不必担心,你没有打扰.
Cindy: Don't worry, you didn't.
迈克,请不要误解我,你是个没用的人.
Mike, please don't take this the wrong way, you're a dud.
戴维∶迈克,我必须和你谈谈.
David: Mike, I have to talk to you.
迈克∶好,可以.
Mike: Sure, OK.
戴维∶我想让你帮我个忙.
David: I gotta ask you a flavour.
迈克∶好吧,说.
Mike: OK, ask.
戴维∶我想知道凯特为什么不开心.
David: I gotta find out what's bothering Kate.
迈克∶啊哈.
Mike: Ah ha.
戴维∶事情发生了变化.
David: Something's changed.
迈克∶啊哈.
Mike: Ah ha.
戴维∶她说什么需要多一些空间,要重新定义我们的关系,
David: She's talking about...
我们的需要,都是些乱七八糟的话.
needing some space, re-defining our relationship, our needs, crazy stuff.
迈克∶啊哈.
Mike: Ah ha.
戴维∶我无法和她谈.
David: I can't talk to her.
迈克∶啊哈.
Mike: Ah ha.
戴维∶你帮我去,好吗?
David: Will you?
迈克∶啊?我帮什么?
Mike: Will I what?
戴维∶你帮我去和她谈话,好吗?
David: Will you talk to her?
迈克∶你是说让我和她谈谈什么让她烦恼?
Mike: You mean, about what's bothering her?
戴维∶迈克,我必须知道,
David: Mike, I need to know, alright?
对吧?
And she likes you, and I mean hey,
她喜欢你,我是说你最近吻她吻的比我还多.
you've been kissing her more lately than I have.
迈克∶嗨,是你让我吻的.
Mike: Hey, you made me.
戴维∶嘿,迈克,
David: Hey, look, Mike, I know;
我明白你夹在中间很难做,但是...
it's very difficult to be put in the middle situations like this, but...
迈克∶哦,你没谱儿.
Mike: Oh, you have no idea.
戴维∶听我说,你是我唯一的希望!
David: Well, listen to me, you're my only hope!Alright?
我昨天晚上试着去和她谈,试着敞开心扉,
I tried to talk to her last night, I tried to get her to open up,
但是,我们却吵到黎明.
but we ended up fighting till dawn.
迈克∶你们吵架了?
Mike: You guys fought?
戴维∶是的.
David: Yeah.
迈克∶哦,太好了...
Mike: Oh, that's great...err...
你们之间仍然还有激情.
that you guys still have that kind of passion between you.
戴维∶迈克,除非你答应我跟她去谈,否则我不会离开的.
David: Look, Mike, I'm not leaving until you tell me you'll talk to her.
索恩教授∶我的演员们,
Professor Thorn: I know Seven a.
我知道早上7点是有点早,但是,
m is very early my fellow thespians,
这次练习的目的就是要激发内在的激情.
but the purpose of this exercise is to tap the inner passions.
凯撒∶我已经准备好了,先生!
Kaiser: I'm ready to tap, sir!
索恩教授∶好样的恺撒.现在我要听到激情!释放内心的激情!
Professor Thorn: Good Tizer, good.Now I want to hear the passion!
出去!出去,所有的人都到外面去!
Release the beast within.Get out!Out, all of you, out!
凯撒∶真是个有趣的教授,我以前还从来没有释放过激情呢.
Kaiser: This was fun professor, I've never released my beast before.
那你想什么时候开始排练?
So when do you wanna start rehearsing?
迈克∶排练什么?
Mike: Rehearsing what?
凯撒∶当你还在睡觉的时候,我替我们俩报了名参加推销员之死的其中一幕的演出,所以,
Kaiser: While you were sleeping, I volunteered us to a scene from, Death of a Salesman.So,
你想要淹谁,是威利罗曼还是他的妻子?
who do you wanna be, Willie Lowman, or his wife?
迈克∶猜猜.
Mike: Guess.
凯撒∶哦,拜托,我们不能2个都演他的妻子.
Kaiser: Oh, come on, we can't both be the wife!
索恩教授:两个人一起享受天堂生活是很幸福的.
Professor Thorn: It is so nice to share my time in hell with another human
being.
凯特:迈克,我想跟你谈谈,这次逃不掉了.
Kate: Mike, I wanna talk to you and this time you're not going anywhere.
迈克:凯特,如果有人需要谈谈的话,那应该是你和戴维.
Mike: Well, look Kate, if someone should do some talking, it's you and David.
凯特∶我知道你的想法,但是,我不会感激你的.
Kate: I know what you're doing, and I don't appreciate it.
迈克:啊?
Mike: Huh?
凯特∶告诉我你不是想迫使我做出决定,
Kate: Oh, tell me you didn't ask out little miss bimbo to force me into
才约白痴小姐出去的.
making a decision.
迈克∶不是,那是我爸爸的主意.
Mike: Err...I didn't, it was my Dad's idea.
凯特∶好,你现在是不是要告诉我,她不是白痴,哈? 哈?
Kate: Right, and now you're gonna tell me she wasn't a bimbo, huh?huh?
迈克∶好了,她很白痴.
Mike: Alright, alright, there was a high level of bimbosity there.
凯特∶迈克.
Kate: Mike...
迈克∶凯特,我为什么要向你解释辛蒂的事情呢?啊?根本就不关你的事.就像我在你宿舍门口等你等到黎明,而你却不知道去了哪里一样,那也不关我的事.凯特,我只是想离你和戴维远点.但是,他刚刚却跑过来跳到我的床上求我,而你呢,也过来质问我关于一个连拼写都不会的女孩子的事.对...但是她会说.
Mike: Look Kate, what am I explaining Cindy to you for, huh?It's really none
of your business.Just like it's none of my business where you were when I
was waiting outside your dorm for you, till dawn.Look Kate, I'm just trying to
stay away from you and David.But now I've got him coming over and jumping
in my bed, and you coming over and grilling me about some girl who can't
even spell, yes...But she can sure say it
凯特∶你等了我一夜!
Kate: You waited for me, till dawn!
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
凯特∶迈克,那天晚上戴维和我只是在吵架.
Kate: Mike, David and I just argued, that's all.
迈克∶我知道,他跟我说过了.他请求我去找出你们俩之间的问题.喔,真是太滑稽了.
Mike: Yeah, I heard.He told me that when he asked me to find out
what's wrong between you guys.Woo, big news story
凯特∶我已经尝试跟他解释了,可是他就是听不进去,他就是一个死板的人.
Kate: I have tried to tell him, he just won't listen, he's so bull-headed.
迈克∶凯特,我正在尝试着不做错事,
Mike: Look, Kate, I'm just trying to do the right thing here.
所以我试图把你从我的脑海里赶出来,可是都无济于事.
You know I'm trying to get you out of my mind, but it's not working.
凯特∶好的.
Kate: Good.
凯撒∶迈克,我仔细想过了,
Kaiser: Mike, I thought it over and I've been a pig; you can be my wife,
我真是笨死了,你可以演我的妻子,我演你的威利.
and I'll be your Willy.
(迈克的梦)
(Mike's dream)
戴维∶迈克,迈克,凯特跟你说什么了?
David: Mike, Mike, what did Kate say?
迈克∶戴维,没必要让你继续受折磨了,实话跟你说,
Mike: Look David, there's no need to put you through this torture;
凯特不爱你了,她爱的是我,我也爱她.
Kate doesn't love you, she loves me and I love her.
戴维∶什么?你抢走了我的女朋友!
David: What?You took my girl!You took my one reason for living!
你抢走了我生存的唯一意义!你还不如直接杀了我?
When don't you just shoot me?
迈克∶你为什么要打死他?
Mike: What'd you shoot him for?
凯特∶为了我们.我要搜查他的皮夹.
Kate: For us.I'll go through his wallet.
迈克∶但是,那相当于是偷窃了.
Mike: But...but that would be stealing.
凯特∶难道抢走我就不是了吗?
Kate: But taking me wasn't!
迈克∶不,不,不,凯特,
Mike: No, no, no, Kat look, this is not how it's supposed to go.
这不是我们的计划.所有的事情都错了,除了那套衣服.
Look, this is all wrong...except for that outfit.
凯特∶你是真的喜欢还是只是说说而已?
Kate: Do you really like it or are you just saying that?
迈克∶凯特,凯特,注意!这样才是对的.
Mike: Kate, Kate, pay attention, come on!This is how it's gonna go.
戴维∶迈克,迈克,凯特跟你说什么了?
David: Mike, Mike, what did Kate say?
迈克∶戴维,没必要让你继续受折磨了,实话跟你说,凯特不爱你了,她爱的是我,我也爱她.
Mike: Look David, there's no need to put you through this torture.Kate doesn't love you, she loves me, and I love her.
戴维∶哦!好.
David: Oh, OK.
迈克∶好!你难道不生气吗?
Mike: OK!You mean, you're not mad!
戴维∶我为什么要生气?我知道你们只是朋友而已,
David: Why should I be mad?
不会做出这样的事情.
I mean I know you two are just friends, you didn't plan any of this.
是我让你们在戏里深情的接吻的.
I'm the one who made you kiss in that play.
如果说有人要道歉的话,那也应该是我.
I mean, if anyone should be apologizing, that's me.
迈克∶哦,我还以为你最少会有一点点的生气呢.
Mike: Oh, well, I thought that you'd be a little bit angry.
戴维∶好了,我为你们俩高兴还来不及呢,
David: Come on, I'm too happy for you two kids, to be mad.
怎么会生气呢.要是凯特也在这里就好了,我们可以一起分享这份喜悦.
I just wish Katy was here to share in this joy.
凯特∶迈克,这件怎么样?
Kate: How's this one, Mike?
戴维∶喔!你们俩现在越来越谈的来了,还是其他的什么?
David: Ooooowweee!Now are you two kids gonna have some fun, or what?
迈克∶是谁?
Mike: Oh, who's that?
戴维∶是我!
David: That's me!
迈克∶但是你在这里呀.
Mike: But you're here.
戴维∶哦!我不在.
David: Oh, no I'm not.
戴维∶(戴维正在撞门)迈克!迈克!迈克!你醒了吗?
David: (David is banging at the door) Mike!Mike!Mike!Did I wake you?
迈克∶没有戴维,我正在睁开眼睛.
Mike: No David, I was in the middle of a really long blink.
戴维∶对不起,我睡不着.
David: Sorry, I couldn't sleep.
迈克∶你要和我一起睡?
Mike: Well couldn't you have not slept back at your place?
戴维∶我知道你和凯特谈过了.
David: I know you talked to Kate.
迈克∶你知道?
Mike: You do?
戴维∶她只告诉我你们谈过了.
David: Well she told me that much, but that's all.
迈克∶听着,戴维,
Mike: Well look David, if Kate doesn't wanna tell you what's bothering her,
如果凯特不想告诉你什么在烦着她,我认为不应该由我....
then I don't think it's my place to be...
戴维∶迈克!我快要疯掉了!
David: Mike!I'm going crazy here!
我要知道,就算是结束也比这样好.
I gotta know, I mean, even if it's over it would be better than this.
迈克∶是吗?
Mike: It would?
戴维∶任何结果都比现在好.迈克,凯特到底说什么了?
David: Anything would be better than this.Mike, what did Kate say?
迈克∶戴维,我们是朋友,对吧?我们也没有料到会发生这样的事情,我们也没有在你背后做什么不好的事情!只是在演完那部戏后,我们才知道自己的真正感觉.
Mike: Look David, we were just friends, alright?Look we didn't plan for any of this to happen, and nothing went on behind your back!We only found out how we felt after we did that play together.
戴维∶什么?你在说什么?
David: What...what are you talking about?
迈克∶没必要再让你受折磨了,凯特不爱你了,她现在爱的是我,我也爱她.我们不愿看到你受到任何的伤害.你看,我像朋友一样的坦诚的对你.
Mike: Look, there's no reason to put you through this torture, Kate doesn't love you, she loves me and I love her.And the last thing we wanted was to hurt you...honest, look, I give you my word as your friend.
戴维∶朋友!
David: Friend!
迈克∶我们完全没有料到会是这样的,但是,事情还是发生了.
Mike: This wasn't how it was meant to go, at all.But this is how
it went
迈克∶凯特!凯特,醒醒!
Mike: Kate!Kate, come on, wake up!
凯特∶迈克!
Kate: Mike!
迈克∶对,是我,快开门.
Mike: Yeah, it's me.Come on, open the door.
凯特∶迈克,大半夜的发生了什么事情?
Kate: Mike, it's the middle of the night.What's going on?
迈克∶凯特,发生大事了.
Mike: Look Kate, this just can't wait.
凯特∶哦!迈克,你的眼睛怎么会这样?
Kate: Oh Mike, look what happened to your eye.
迈克∶我知道,戴维过来找我,
Mike: I know, look,
我正在半梦半醒之间,
David came over and I was half a sleep and I didn't mean to tell him,
我根本不想告诉他的,但是...
but...
凯特∶告诉他什么?
Kate: Tell him what?
迈克∶他知道我跟你谈过了,你也知道他是个急性子,所以我告诉了他,我就是你们俩之间的问题.然后他就打了我!
Mike: Look, he knew that I'd talked to you but, you know what a hot-head David can be; so I told him that I was the reason that you two were having problems.He hit me!
凯特∶什么?
Kate: What?
迈克∶你能相信吗,他打我?
Mike: Yeah, can you believe, he hit me?
凯特∶你告诉他我们的事!
Kate: You told him about us!
迈克∶是的.至少现在大家都知道了...
Mike: Yes, look, at least now it's out in the open and David knows...
最坏的也就是结束你们的关系!你打我!
the worst is over now!You hit me!
凯特∶你怎么敢告诉他我们的事情?你给我出去!出去!出去!
Kate: How dare you tell him about us?Get out!Get out!Get out!
迈克∶如果这就是你的态度,我马上就走.
Mike: Well if that's your attitude, I'm leaving.
杰森∶迈克,你说的我都能理解.唯一不能理解的是,凯特为什么要打你呢?
Jason: I understand everything you said, Mike.The only thing I don't get is why Kate hit you.
麦琪∶哦,我完全能理解.
Maggie: Oh, it makes perfect sense to me.
迈克∶对,女人都是疯子!对吧,爸爸?
Mike: Yeah, women are nuts!Right, Dad?
杰森∶嘿,心理学家很少使用这个词的,疯子...除非我们不想活了.
Jason: Hey, hey.Well, Psychiatrists rarely like to use the term, nuts...besides we're out of steaks.
麦琪∶迈克,你根本无权告诉戴维关于凯特的感觉.
Maggie: Mike, you had no business telling David how Kate felt.
她一定是想自己亲口对他说,如果是我,我也想.
She probably wanted to do that herself, I would.
迈克∶如果是这样的话,那她为什么不说?
Mike: Well then, why didn't she?
麦琪∶她一定对戴维有着很深的感情,
Maggie: Well she probably has pretty deep feelings for David,
这份感情肯定已经维持了很长一段时间了.
feelings that have been around a long time.
迈克∶那她为什么会爱上我呢?
Mike: Well then, how can she be so crazy about me?
麦琪∶迈克,你根本不知道她是否爱你,
Maggie: Mike, you don't know if she's crazy about you,
你也不知道,
and you don't know if she's crazy about David,
她是否爱戴维,你根本没有给她选择的机会.
you never gave her a chance to decide.
迈克∶嘿,但是总要有人去说呀.
Mike: Hey, well somebody had to say something.
麦琪∶如此的...
Maggie: Oh, that is so...male!
男人!
Well you see things your way,
你只不过是用你自己的方式来看问题,所以你以为其他所有的人都和你有一样的想法;所以你就鲁莽行事,
and you assume that everybody else sees things the same way;
难道有人会因此受到伤害也没有关系吗?
so you act and it doesn't matter who you hurt?
迈克∶我伤害了谁!哦,
Mike: Who I hurt!
对不起,妈妈,
Oh, I'm sorry, Mom,
原谅我这么自私的行为,我是自作自受.
excuse me for being so thoughtless and landing my face under their fists.
麦琪∶杰森,我很惊奇你居然没有告诉他要远离他们,
Maggie: Jason, I'm surprised you didn't tell him to stay away until they
直到他们解决好整件事情.
worked this thing out.
杰森∶我原原本本的跟他说过了.
Jason: That's exactly what I told him.
麦琪∶那你的儿子是怎么得到这些打伤的黑眼圈的,哈?哈?
Maggie: Well then, how did our son get those shiners, huh?Huh?
杰森∶迈克,你说的对,女人都是疯子.
Jason: You know...You're right, women are nuts.
麦琪∶但是我们的听力却很好!
Maggie: But we do have excellent hearing!
开萝尔∶迈克..
Carol: Mike...
迈克∶开萝尔,我现在最不希望看到的就是你..
Mike: Look Carol, the last thing I need right now is you, alright?
开萝尔∶迈克,我不是来幸灾乐祸的,也不是来在你伤口撒盐的.
Carol: Mike, I'm not here to gloat or to take pleasure in your pain.
迈克∶你不是吗?
Mike: You're not?
开萝尔∶我刚好在大厅听见你的经历,
Carol: Well, I was eaves-dropping on the in the hall and I heard what
听到那些真的让我觉得很难过,因为你试着去做对的事,
you went through, and I'm really sorry because it sounds like you tried
但是没人让你去做.
to do the right thing, but nobody would let you.
迈克∶对,对,那是事实.
Mike: Well, well yeah, that's true.
开萝尔∶我还想告诉你的是,妈妈可能做的不是很对,
Carol: And I just wanted you to know that Mom was a little base,
而爸爸是对的,女人有时会比较敏感.
and Dad was right; women can be a tad insensitive.
迈克∶天哪,开萝尔,我都不知道要说什么了.
Mike: Well gosh, Carol, I don't know what to say.
开萝尔∶说明白就好了.
Carol: Say cheese.Got it.
凯撒:教授,
Kaiser: Great class today, professor,
今天的课真棒.
and thanks for those super duper acting tips.
索恩教授∶别客气凯撒,从一个将来的银行支票员最里听到这些,
Professor Thorn: Don't mention it Kaiser,
对我意义重大.
that means a lot coming from a future bank teller.
试镜员∶哦,迈克.
Kaiser: Oh, Mike...
索恩教授∶不,不,
Professor Thorn: No, no, Kaiser, for the twentieth time,
凯撒,第20次的告诉你,我没有戏服!
I do not have my dress for our scene!
凯撒∶女人都是疯子.
Kaiser: Women are nuts.
迈克:戴维,
Mike: Hey David, hey err...
我只是想说告诉你凯特的想法是我不好,
I just wanted to say that I was wrong for telling you what Kate wanted
我没有证据,现在我理智多了.
because I don't have a clue as to what Kate wants, and err...
我会离开,
those things that I said, they were more wishful thinking than anything else.
非常抱歉,
I got carried away and I'm sorry, I...I...
真心希望你们能够和好.
really hope that you two can work things out.
戴维∶对,没错.
David: Yeah right.
迈克∶嘿,我真的想让你知道,
Mike: Hey, look man, I really want you to know that...
我是真的很抱歉,我仍然把你当朋友.
that I'm truly sorry and...and I think of you as a friend.
戴维∶现在说这些已经没有任何意义了,知道吗?
David: Well...on another day that might mean something, alright?
凯特∶你好.
Kate: Hi.
迈克∶你好.
Mike: Hi.
凯特∶我等了你好久.
Kate: I've been waiting for you.
迈克∶凯特,
Mike: Hey look, Kate,
我要你知道我已经向戴维解释过了,
I just want you to know that I've already explained to David that I was
我不应该替你说话.
completely out of line by speaking for you.
凯特∶没有,你没有.
Kate: No, you weren't.
迈克∶你说什么.
Mike: Pardon me.
凯特∶就算你是不应该,但是,那却是该做的事情.
Kate: Well, even though you shouldn't have, it was the right thing to do.
迈克:你看,凯特,你再打我一次也不为过.
Mike: Look, Kate, I think it would be a lot easier if you'd just hit
me again
凯特∶哦,迈克...
Kate: Oh Mike...
迈克∶凯特,我还想让你知道的是,
Mike: Look Kate, I just want you to know that I am going to back off,
我决定要退出了,直到你们俩找出真正的原因...
OK, until you and David can figure out whatever it is between you guys...
凯特∶迈克...我今天和戴维分手了.
Kate: Mike...I broke up with David today.
迈克∶噢不凯特,我认为你不必为我这样做.
Mike: Oh no, Kate, I don't think you should have done that for me.
凯特∶我不是为你才这样做的,而是为了我自己.
Kate: I didn't do it for you, I did it for me.
其实我们俩很早以前就应该要分手的,
It's something that I should have done a long time ago,
所以当我认识你后,我就决定了.
so then when I met you, anything might have happened.
迈克∶也许?
Mike: Might have?
凯特∶因为戴维不好过,你不好过,我也不好过.
Kate: Look, David feels lousy, you feel lousy, and I feel lousy.
迈克∶你要走了?
Mike: You're leaving?
凯特∶我不知道.
Kate: I don't know.
迈克∶凯特,那你为什么要来?
Mike: Kate, why did you come?
凯特∶我也不知道.
Kate: I'm not sure.
迈克∶如果我现在抱你的话,会不会不合适?凯特∶是不合适,但是,
Mike: Would now be a really bad time to put my arm around you?
我喜欢.00:22:19,500
Kate: Yes, but I'd like it anyway.